Laura E. Green

Email: GreenLaE@outlook.com | Phone: 571-594-6931 | Tucson, AZ 85719

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/laura-g-086284171

Github: MechanicalMouse | Website: mechanicalmouse.github.io

SUMMARY

Web developer with over 8 years of basic forum-based HTML and CSS experience. Continually refining skills in front-end JavaScript, Node.js, and more. Passionate learner, problem solver, and creative thinker. Organized, patient, and driven to ensure high-quality work.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

CSS, SASS, HTML5, Node.js, JavaScript

PROJECTS

Find-A-Recipe | github.com/MechanicalMouse/Find-A-Recipe | mechanicalmouse.github.io/Find-A-Recipe/ Front-End Developer

- Helps in finding a recipe, either with the recipe name or a chosen list of ingredients.
- Used Bootstrap and SASS

Gem Game | github.com/MechanicalMouse/Gem-Game | mechanicalmouse.github.io/Gem-Game/ Front-End Developer

- A simple click game. Use mystery value gems to reach the goal number.
- Used JavaScript, CSS, and HTML

Hamster Trivia | github.com/MechanicalMouse/TriviaGame | mechanicalmouse.github.io/TriviaGame/ Front-end Developer

- A short trivia game about Syrian hamsters.
- Used JavaScript, CSS, and HTML

EXPERIENCE

Mturk Worker – Amazon Mechanical Turk – Tucson, AZ

2019 - Current

Answering surveys, recognizing bots, and labeling and categorizing images and data.

<u>Sewing Contractor</u> – Arizona Apparel Manufacturing, LLC – Tucson, AZ

2018 - 2018

Attached tabs to shoe covers as part of an assembly-line-type production system.

Sabbatical - 2016 - 2017

Took time out of work to care for a family member.

<u>Customer Sales Associate</u> – Walgreens – Fairfax, VA

2014 - 2014

Organized and restocked shelves and helped unload shipments.

EDUCATION

University of Arizona, Tucson, AZ – Full Stack Web Development Bootcamp